[Music]
[Applause]
Market streets riddled with bodies that
sway. Lost in a haze, but they're not
far away. Eyes glazed open, memories
erased. Standing in silence, stuck in
disgrace.
Boss bitty fingers dripping empty
dreams.
Reality buries them under routine.
Statues on the sidewalk, they don't move
or blink. Closing in the moment, caught
on the break. Time's moving faster, but
they're stuck in place.
Concrete confession on every wasted
face. Oh,
stand so still.
Oh, chills and thrills.
[Music]
Sirens pass by, but nobody stirs.
Needles at hand, and nothing deters.
Trees broken down where the pavements
cracked. Shadows alive, but hopes what
they lack.
Sunrise eyes and never see.
Trapped in a loop on Ellis Street.
Statues on the sidewalk, they don't move
or break. Closing in the moment, caught
on the brink. Time moving faster, but
they're stuck in place.
Concrete confession on every wasted
face. Oh,
stand so still. Oh, chills and thrills.
[Music]